RAÚL CASSONE

FULL-STACK DEVELOPER

+34 653 62 69 27

Barcelona, Spain

jrpcassone@gmail.com

maulcassone.io

PROFILE

Web developer with two years of experience, specializing in front-end development, with skills to contribute to backend tasks and project management. I stand out for my excellent communication skills, teamwork abilities, and focus on continuous improvement.

SKILLS

- Node.js
- React Redux
- Eslint
- Next.js
- Postman
- WordPress

- Git
- Styled Components
- Jest
- Sanity Studio
- JWT
- AWS

- TypeScript
- BEM
- React Testing Library
- MongoDB
- MSW
- GraphQL

- Figma
- Sass
- Tailwind CSS
- Shopify
- Github Actions
- Docker

EDUCATION

Full Stack Web Development Bootcamp

ISDI coders 2023

Sound Certificate of Higher Education

CEF Mallorca 2012 - 2014

WORK EXPERIENCE

Fullstack Developer - AMA

Freelance Full-Stack for web development company • July 2024 - Currently

- Website development with Next.Js, WordPress and Sanity studio.
- Self management
- Periodic code reviews

Web development rebranding Dublab Barcelona

Freelance frontend web development | October 2023 - March 2024 (6 months)

- Next.JS, Django, Tailwind CSS, Typescript.
- Complete redesign of the frontend side.
- Rearrangement of existing functionalities.
- Implementation of new features: weekly calendar from third-party API, new endpoint to manage latest content added from the CMS.
- Integration of different APIs for proper display of page content.
- Coordination with backend programmer for the proper implementation of new features and bug correction.

Picnic Sound Studio

Web development March 2022 - July 2023 (1 year and 3 months)

- Website development using basic HTML, CSS, and JavaScript for projects that required websites.
- Establishing work protocols and dynamics.
- Project management and budget negotiations.

Barcelona community Radio

Studio Manager and Technical Lead | 2021 - 2023

- As the studio manager, I was responsible for coordinating the daily schedule, managing hourly distribution, and producing monthly. programs and guests, both in Spanish and English.
- As the technical lead, I was responsible for live and recorded broadcasts and the management of resulting files.
- Organization of complementary activities for the radio: events, content for social media, interviews, technical assistance, etc.
- Coordination and training of volunteers.
- Participation in content direction and platform functionality.

LANGUAGES

• Spanish - Native

Catalán - Native

• English - Fluent